Inventaris van het Archief van de Raad voor de Scheepvaart (1908) 1909-2010
Nationaal Archief, Den Haag
- Bijzonder, B.
  - Taakuitvoering, B.2
    - Onderzoek scheepsongevallen, B.2.7
      - Ter documentatie aangeschafte Zeekaarten, B.2.7.3
        - British Admiralty Charts, B.2.7.3.2
          - Pacific Ocean, B.2.7.3.2.4
            - Coastal waters Australia, B.2.7.3.2.4.2
              - 1037: Flinders Bay, 15th December 1879 (last correction 1956), 3981; blad
              - 1038: Crocodile Islands, Millingimbi Inlet and approaches, 8th December 1944 (revised 1961), 3982; blad
              - 1043: Buccaneer Archipelago, 16th October 1914 (last correction 1953), 3983; blad
              - 1044: Cape Arnhem to Cape Fourcroy, 11th February 1955 (revised 1959), 3984; blad
              - 1045: King Sound - north part, 26th April 1915 (last correction 1953), 3985; blad
              - 1047: Cape Fourcroy to Cape Leveque, 20th January 1956 (revised 1959), 3986; blad
              - 1048: Buccaneer Archipelago to Bedout Island, 14th April 1883 (last correction 1954), 3987; blad
              - 1055: Bedout Island to Cape Cuvier, 5th February 1883 (revised 1960), 3988; blad
              - 1056: Cape Cuvier to Champion Bay, 2nd January 1879 (revised 1960), 3989; blad
              - 1057: Liverpool River, 28th March 1893 (last correction 1919), 3990; blad
              - 1058: Approaches to Fremantle, 22nd July 1955 (last correction 1957), 3991; blad
              - 1059: Doubtful Island Bay to the Head of the Great Australian Bight, 30th November 1881 (last correction 1954), 3992; blad
              - 1061: Cape Catastrophe to the Great Australian Bight, 28th August 1875 (last correction 1956), 3993; blad
              - 1062: Rivoli Bay to Cape Otway, 4th September 1901 (last correction 1956), 3994; blad
              - 1068: Cape Moreton to Sandy Cape, 14th January 1955 (last correction 1956), 3995; blad
              - 1069: Port Jackson, 15th February 1890 (revised 1963), 3996; blad
              - 1070: Port Stephens, 3rd March 1924 (last correction 1953), 3997; blad
              - 1079: Tasmania, 1st October 1860 (last correction 1956), 3998; blad
              - 1079: Tasmania, 1st October 1860 (last correction 1960), 3999; blad
              - 1080: River Tamar - Low Head to Launceston, 31st March 1908 (last correction 1954), 4000; blad
              - 1080: Port Dalrymple and River Tamar, 31st March 1908 (last correction 1958), 4001; blad
              - 1081: George Bay, 15th January 1864 (last correction 1949), 4002; blad
              - 1093: Clarence Strait, 22nd August 1952, 4003; blad
              - 1102: Cleveland Bay - Townsville Harbour, 24th May 1892 (revised 1962), 4004; blad
              - 1115: Western approaches to Clarence Strait, 5th March 1954 (revised 1959), 4005; blad
              - 1110: Norfolk and Philip Islands, 4th April 1856, 4006; blad
              - 1110: Norfolk and Philip Islands, 4th April 1856 (last correction 1956), 4007; blad
              - 1171: Port Phillip, 28th June 1915 (last correction 1960), 4008; blad
              - 1206: Approaches to King Souind, 23rd July 1954 (last correction 1955), 4009; blad
              - 1207: Adèle Island to Lagrange Bay, 15th October 1954, 4010; blad
              - 1211: Gabo Island to Port Jackson, 8th November 1888 (last correction 1959), 4011; blad
              - 1242: Cape Voltaire to Adèle Island, 7th May 1954, 4012; blad
              - 1243: Cape Londonderry to Cape Voltaire, 2nd July 1954 (revised 1959), 4013; blad
              - 1254: Fantome Island to Dunk Island including Hinchinbrook Channel, 30th October 1933 (last correction 1956), 4014; blad
              - 1333: Port Essington, 21st September 1840 (last correction 1945), 4015; blad
              - 1350: Cooktown Harbour, 11th September 1893 (last correction 1952), 4016; blad
              - 1387: Lacrosse Island to Reveley Island, 12th March 1891 (last correction 1951), 4017; blad
              - 1388: Cambridge Gulf, 20th February 1891 (last correction 1948), 4018; blad
              - 1379: Plans in New South Wales, 18th March 1935 (last correction 1956), 4019; blad
              - 1418: Princess Royal Harbour, 18th January 1892, 4020; blad
              - 1437: Port Hedland, 10th November 1897 (last correction 1955), 4021; blad
              - 1472: Koombana Bay - Hamelin Bay and inner harbour, 11th November 1898 (revised 1961), 4022; blad
              - 1475: Port Arthur, 27th November 1893 (last correction 1941), 4023; blad
              - 1629: Macquarie Harbour, 29th August 1933 (last correction 1956), 4024; blad
              - 1670: Approaches to Moreton Bay, 31st August 1951 (last correction 1955), 4025; blad
              - 1673: Approaches to Brisbane, 3rd November 1950 (last correction 1959), 4026; blad
              - 1674: Brisbane River, 3rd June 1960 (revised 1963), 4027; blad
              - 1694: Anchorages in Bass Strait, 1st July 1868 (last correction 1955), 4028; blad
              - 1695a: Bass Strait - eastern sheet, date unknown (last correction 1954), 4029; blad
              - 1695b: Bass Strait - western sheet, 27th April 1868 (last correction 1956), 4030; blad
              - 1700: Fremantle Harbour and Gage Roads, 2nd May 1952 (revised 1962), 4031; blad
              - 1703: Cape Liptrap to Kent Group, 5th August 1960, 4032; blad
              - 1704: Adam Bay and entrance of the Adelaide River, 10th January 1864 (last correction 1950), 4033; blad
              - 1706: Banks Strait, 1st February 1878 (last correction 1954), 4034; blad
              - 1707: Westernport, 31st December 1949 (last correction 1956), 4035; blad
              - 1716: Jones Island to Cape Voltaire including the Holothuria Banks, 4th May 1893 (last correction 1956), 4036; blad
              - 1723: Houtman Rocks and adjacent coast, 26th August 1845 (last correction 1956), 4037; blad
              - 1725: Champion Bay, 10th June 1950 (last correction 1956), 4038; blad
              - 1750: Port Adelaide Harbour - Port Adelaide and approaches, 20th March 1953 (revised 1960), 4039; blad
              - 1762: Gulf of St. Vincent and approaches, 9th November 1956 (last correction 1963), 4040; blad
              - 1807: Carpentaria Gulf - southern part, 11th May 1847 (last correction 1951), 4041; blad
              - 1900: Port Curtis - Gladstone Harbour, 8th May 1959, 4042; blad
              - 1937: Adolphus Channel, 9th October 1953, 4043; blad
              - 1952: Port Clinton, 31st July 1849 (last correction 1952), 4044; blad
              - 2119: Newcastle Harbour, 21st November 1916 (last correction 1957), 4045; blad
              - 2321: Torres Strait and approaches, 29th April 1955 (last correction 1958), 4046; blad
              - 2344: Frankland Islands to Lizard Island, 5th February 1960, 4047; blad
              - 2349: Palm Isles to Frankland Islands, 13th November 1959, 4048; blad
              - 2350: Double Point to Cape Grafton, 21st January 1899 (last corrrection 1955), 4049; blad
              - 2354: Cape Sidmouth to Cape York, 13th July 1956, 4050; blad
              - 2355: Lizard Island to Cape Sidmouth, 4th September 1959, 4051; blad
              - 2389: St. Vincent and Spencer Gulfs, 25th November 1913 (last correction 1956), 4052; blad
              - 2493: Ports Noarlunga and Willunga - Victor Harbour and Port Elliot, 1st July 1870 (last correction 1951), 4053; blad
              - 2619: King George Sound and Princess Royal Harbour, 13th October 1879, 4054; blad
              - 2731: Geelong Harbour and approaches, 7th March 1958, 4055; blad
              - 2747: Entrance to Port Phillip, 27th February 1903 (last correction 1956), 4056; blad
              - 2759a: Australia - northern portion, 28th December 1934 (revised 1967), 4057; blad
              - 2759b: Australia - southern portion, 20th July 1885 (revised 1961), 4058; blad
              - 2763: Coral Sea and Great Barrier Reefs - southern sheet, 19th December 1860 (last correction 1956), 4059; blad
              - 2764: Coral Sea and Great Barrier Reefs - northern sheet, 9th June 1886 (last correction 1956), 4060; blad
              - 2803: Port Denison, 15th May 1889 (last correction 1952), 4061; blad
              - 2921: Claremont Point to Cape Direction, 18th March 1899 (last correction 1953), 4062; blad
              - 2922: Turtle Group to Claremont Point, 4th July 1891 (last correction 1955), 4063; blad
              - 2923: Hope Islands to Turtle Group, 4th July 1891 (last correction 1952), 4064; blad
              - 2924: Cape Grafton to Hope Islands, 25th January 1892 (last correction 1955), 4065; blad
              - 2928: Great North East Channel, Bramble Cay to Arden Islet, 7th November 1952 (last correction 1953), 4066; blad
              - 2929: Great North East Channel - Arden Islet to Twin Island, 7th August 1953 (last correction 1957), 4067; blad
              - 3088: Howick Island, Night Island, Cape Weymouth and Home Islands anchorages, 30th June 1899 (last correction 1956), 4068; blad
              - 3090: Pavilion Point to Dowsing Point, 27th October 1899 (last correction 1958), 4069; blad
              - 3133: Cairns Harbour, 19th February 1901 (last correction 1957), 4070; blad
              - 3155: Flinders Group, 9th February 1901 (last correction 1948), 4071; blad
              - 3169: Port Philip to Gabo Island, 27th February 1902 (last correction 1960), 4072; blad
              - 3179: Starvation Boat Harbour, 11th January 1902 (last correction 1956), 4073; blad
              - 3186: Mary Anne Passage and approaches, 30th November 1901 (last correction 1959), 4074; blad
              - 3187: Mangrove Islands to North West Cape, 27th December 1901 (last correction 1952), 4075; blad
              - 3189: Cape Le Grand to Cape Pasley, 27th February 1902 (last correction 1948), 4076; blad
              - 3221: Duke of Orleans Bay and Goose Island Bay, 31st December 1901 (last correction 1956), 4077; blad
              - 3254: Norman River Entrance, 27th January 1902 (last correction 1952), 4078; blad
              - 3410: Port Davey - Bathurst Channel - outer sheet, 17th December 1928 (last correction 1940), 4079; blad
              - 3411: Bathurst Channel - inner sheet, Bathurst Harbour, 17th December 1928, 4080; blad
              - 3641: Backstairs Passage, 8th December 1961, 4081; blad
              - 3649: Entrance to Port Dalrymple, 12th August 1907 (last correction 1958), 4082; blad
              - 3687: Albatross Island to Rocky Cape, 29th February 1916 (last correction 1953), 4083; blad
              - 3719: Marion Reef, 24th November 1908 (last correction 1944), 4084; blad
              - 3762: Hay Island to Bow Reef, 5th September 1911 (last correction 1950), 4085; blad
              - 3781: Wednesday Island to Booby Island including Prince of Wales Channel, 21st November 1952 (last correction 1957), 4086; blad
              - 3782: Endeavour Strait - western sheet, 28th August 1953, 4087; blad
              - 3783: Endeavour Strait - eastern sheet, 11th December 1953 (last correction 1954), 4088; blad
              - 4726: Cape Leeuwin to Esperance, 17th March 1989, 4089; blad
            - Coastal waters Caroline Islands, B.2.7.3.2.4.3
              - 763: Caroline Islands - western portion, 17th April 1930 (revised 1960), 4090; blad
              - 764: Caroline Islands - eastern portion, 17th April 1930 (revised 1960), 4091; blad
              - 772: Islands and anchorages in the Caroline Islands, 6th September 1929 (revised 1961), 4092; blad
              - 909: Islands and anchorages in the Caroline Islands, 1st March 1929 (last correction 1951), 4093; blad
              - 970: Islands and anchorages in the Caroline Islands, 6th September 1929 (revised 1960), 4094; blad
              - 977: Islands and anchorages in the Caroline Islands, 4th August 1928 (last correction 1957), 4095; blad
              - 978: Islands and anchorages in the Caroline Islands, 24th May 1929 (last correction 1951), 4096; blad
              - 981: Senyavin Islands, 9th April 1928 (last correction 1956), 4097; blad
              - 982: Truk or Hogolu Islands, 24th May 1929 (last correction 1957), 4098; blad
              - 1485: Yap Island, 11th June 1928 (last correction 1957), 4099; blad
            - Coastal waters New Zealand, B.2.7.3.2.4.4
              - 695: Cook Strait, 1st October 1954 (revised 1963), 4100; blad
              - 1022: Macquarie, Auckland, Campbell, Antipodes and Bounty Islands, 20th March 1917 (last correction 1958), 4101; blad
              - 1090: Bay of Islands - Whangarei Harbour, 21st August 1942 (revised 1960), 4102; blad
              - 1090: Bay of Islands - Whangarei Harbour, 21st August 1942 (revised 1960) (last correction 1962), 4103; blad
              - 1212: New Zealand, 20th June 1885 (last correction 1957), 4104; blad
              - 1212: New Zealand, 20th June 1885 (last correction 1958), 4105; blad
              - 1423: Port Nicholson - Lambton Harbour and Evans Bay, 28th January 1955 (last correction 1958), 4106; blad
              - 1493: Queen Charlotte Sound - eastern sheet, 4th August 1950 (last correction 1957), 4107; blad
              - 1494: Queen Charlotte Sound - western sheet, 4th August 1950 (last correction 1958), 4108; blad
              - 1512: Plans on the north coast of North Island, 29th May 1924 (revised 1960), 4109; blad
              - 1896: Approaches to Auckland, 23rd January 1931 (last correction 1958), 4110; blad
              - 1915: Nugget Point to Centre Island, 9th July 1954 (last correction 1957), 4111; blad
              - 1916: Cornish Head to Nugget Point, 28th August 1953 (last correction 1957), 4112; blad
              - 1970: Auckland Harbour, 17th June 1955 (revised 1961), 4113; blad
              - 1998: Omaha Bay to Tiri-Tiri Matangi including Kawau Bay, 17th February 1906 (last correction 1957), 4114; blad
              - 1999: Lyttelton Harbour - Lyttelton - Akaroa Harbour, 17th May 1957 (last correction 1958), 4115; blad
              - 2411: Otago Harbour, 27th December 1957 (last correction 1958), 4116; blad
              - 2512: Gable End Foreland to Napier, 29th July 1960, 4117; blad
              - 2513: Napier Road - Breakwater Harbour, 23rd August 1957, 4118; blad
              - 2513: Napier Road - Breakwater Harbour, 23rd August 1957 (last correction 1960), 4119; blad
              - 2518: Napier to Castle Point, 6th February 1959, 4120; blad
              - 2519: Castle Point to Cape Palliser, 6th June 1958, 4121; blad
              - 2521: Tauranga Harbour, 15th March 1957 (revised 1963), 4122; blad
              - 2525: Hokianga to Tutukaka, 2nd November 1857 (last correction 1957), 4123; blad
              - 2526: Taranaki Roads and New Plymouth - Port Taranaki, 15th January 1960, 4124; blad
              - 2527: Mayor Island to Poverty Bay, 23rd July 1906 (revised 1961), 4125; blad
              - 2529: Nelson Roads - Port Nelson, 6th May 1960, 4126; blad
              - 2532: Banks Peninsula to Otago Peninsula, 3rd September 1934 (last correction 1960), 4127; blad
              - 2532: Banks Peninsula to Otago Peninsula, 3rd September 1934 (revised 1961), 4128; blad
              - 2533: Poverty Bay, 28th October 1960, 4129; blad
              - 2535: Manukau Harbour to Cape Egmont, 12th November 1857 (last correction 1958), 4130; blad
              - 2543: Maunganui Bluff to Manukau Harbour and Tutukaka Harbour to Mayor Island including Hauraki Gulf, 4th February 1908 (last correction 1957), 4131; blad
              - 2544: Cape Palliser to Kaikoura Peninsula, 22nd June 1956, 4132; blad
              - 2545: Kaikoura Peninsula to Banks Peninsula, 12th October 1956 (last correction 1957), 4133; blad
              - 2553: Approaches to Greymouth and Westport, 12th August 1960, 4134; blad
              - 2589: Foveaux Strait to Awarua River, 20th October 1858 (last correction 1957), 4135; blad
              - 2590: River Awarua to River Waiau, 1st July 1858 (last correction 1957), 4136; blad
              - 2591: River Waiho to Cape Foulwind, 1st July 1858 (last correction 1958), 4137; blad
              - 2616: Karamea River to Stephens Island, 17th August 1962, 4138; blad
              - 3332: Mercury Bay to Town Point, 8th August 1903 (revised 1963), 4139; blad
              - 3484: Bluff Harbour and approaches - Paterson Inlet, 22nd July 1955 (revised 1962), 4140; blad
              - 3500: Cape Runway to Gable End Foreland, 28th October 1905 (last correction 1957), 4141; blad
              - 3565: Bream Head to Tepaki Point including Hauraki Gulf, 28th July 1906 (last correction 1958), 4142; blad
              - 3633: New Zealand - north island, 15th February 1950 (revised 1962), 4143; blad
              - 3634: New Zealand - south island, 15th February 1950 (revised 1962), 4144; blad
              - 3797: Great Barrier Island to Mayor Island including Hauraki Gulf, 29th January 1943 (last correction 1958), 4145; blad
              - 3798: Cape Brett to Cuvier Island, 7th April 1944 (last correction 1957), 4146; blad
              - 5212: Plans between Whangamumu and Omaha Cove, October 1980, published by the Hydrographic Office of the Royal New Zealand Navy, Auckland, 4147; blad
            - Coastal waters west coast South America, B.2.7.3.2.4.5
              - 537: Plans on the coast of Chile, 16th February 1962 (revised 1961), 4148; blad
              - 559: Chili - anchorages in Tierra del Fuego, 9th December 1886 (revised 1964), 4149; blad
              - 570: Plans on the coast of Chile, 30th November 1962 (revised 1986), 4150; blad
              - 586: Rio Guayas and approaches, 12th October 1973 (revised 1990), 4151; blad
              - 630: Canal Smyth to Canal Señoret, published on 5th March 1954 (revised 1983), 4152; blad
              - 645: Plans on the coast of Peru, 21st October 1909 (last correction 1960), 4153; blad
              - 783: Pacific Ocean - south east sheet, 31st March 1875 (revised 1960), 4154; blad
              - 1279: Punta Pescadores to Bahia Independencia, 29th December 1840 (last correction 1961), 4155; blad
              - 1283: Cabo Lobos to Punta Pescadores, 15th September 1840 (revised 1961), 4156; blad
              - 1285: Begueta Bay to River Chicama, 15th September 1840 (last correction 1959), 4157; blad
              - 1290: Plans in the Golfo Corcovado, 5th August 1955, 4158; blad
              - 1294: Plans on the coast of Peru, 14th August 1893 (last correction 1960), 4159; blad
              - 1314: Ports and anchorages on the coast of Chile, 2nd June 1924 (revised 1959), 4160; blad
              - 1319: Bahia Concepcion, 21st October 1926 (last correction 1961), 4161; blad
              - 1323: Bahia Independencia to Bahia Begueta, 15th September 1840 (revised 1959), 4162; blad
              - 1335: Rio Chicama to Puerto de Paita,26th January 1841 (last correction 1959), 4163; blad
              - 1340: Plans on the coast of Peru, 19th November 1894 (revised 1963), 4164; blad
              - 1347: Plans on the coast of Peru, 19th November 1894 (last correction 1961), 4165; blad
              - 1375: Archipiélago de Colón (Galapagos Islands), 4th September 1953 (last correction 1959), 4166; blad
              - 1383: Juan Fernandez - Mas a Fuera - St. Felix and St. Ambrose Islands, 4th October 1901 (last correction 1961), 4167; blad
              - 1427: Lake Washington Ship Canal - Seattle and Tacoma Harbours, 6th December 1935 (last correction 1957), 4168; blad
              - 1782: Bahia Pisco to Punta de Santa Elena, 20th November 1903 (last correction 1959), 4169; blad
              - 1813: Puerto de Paita to Punta Ayangui, 1st October 1847 (last correction 1960), 4170; blad
              - 1814: Ayangui Point to Verde Point, 29th September 1847 (revised 1959), 4171; blad
              - 1853: Approaches to Bahia del Callao - Puerto del Callao, 23rd December 1937 (last correction 1959), 4172; blad
              - 2257: Punta Verde to Buenaventura, 18th July 1854 (revised 1959), 4173; blad
              - 2258: Buenaventura to Cabo Marzo, 18th July 1854 (last correction 1960), 4174; blad
              - 2318: Approaches to Bahia Buenaventura, 5th May 1972 (revised 1978) (last correction 1992), 4175; blad
              - 2319: Bahia Buenventura - Buenaventura inner harbour, 5th September 1854 (revised 1963), 4176; blad
              - 2332: Bahia Ferrol and Bahia de Coisco, 28th February 1899 (last correction 1955), 4177; blad
              - 2987: Plans on the coast of Chile, 22nd December 1938 (revised 1970), 4178; blad
              - 3070: Bahia Algodonales to Rada de Arica, 22nd December 1938 (revised 1960), 4179; blad
              - 3071: Puerto Pan de Azucar to Bahia Algodonales, 22nd December 1938 (revised 1960), 4180; blad
              - 3072: Caleta Totoralillo to Puerto Pan de Azucar, 22nd December 1938 (last correction 1950), 4181; blad
              - 3073: Bahia Valparaiso to Caleta Totoralillo, 29th June 1942 (last correction 1960), 4182; blad
              - 3074: Golfo de Arauco to Bahia Valparaiso, 12th December 1947 (last correction 1960), 4183; blad
              - 3076: Mejillones del Sur - Iquique, 31st March 1939 (last correction 1961), 4184; blad
              - 3077: Rada Blanco Encalada - Rada de Antofagasta - Puerto de Tocopilla - Caleta Gatico and Rada de Cobija, 31st March 1939 (last correction 1959), 4185; blad
              - 3078: Puerto Taltal - Caleta Esmeralda - Puertos Caldera and Calderilla, 22nd December 1938 (last correction 1960), 4186; blad
              - 3079: Paso Choros - Puerto Chañaral de las Animas - Caleta del Medio - Puerto Huasco, 10th February 1940 (revised 1964), 4187; blad
              - 3090: Arica to Islotes Infiernillos - Bahia San Juan and Bahia San Nicolas and approaches - Puerto Ilo, 19th April 1974 (last correction 1992), 4188; blad
              - 3318: Punta de Santa Elena to Golfo Dulce, 14th August 1903 (last correction 1960), 4189; blad
              - 3627: Anchorages between Golfo de Trinidad and Golfo de Peñas, 2nd April 1907 (revised 1964), 4190; blad
              - 3747: Iquique to Bahia Pisco, 26th November 1921 (last correction 1961), 4191; blad
              - 3748: Anchorages in archipelago Reina Adelaida, 13th December 1920 (revised 1963), 4192; blad
            - Coastal waters west coast USA, Canada and Central America, B.2.7.3.2.4.6
              - 229: Point Penos to Bodega Head, 31st December 1868 (last correction 1959, 4193; blad
              - 268: Cape Fear to Sapelo Sound, 7th December 1934 (last correction 1957), 4194; blad
              - 455: Anchorages on the coast of California and Oregon, 20th February 1878 (last correction 1955), 4195; blad
              - 516: Ports and anchorages on the west coast of Mexico, 19th May 1961, 4196; blad
              - 573: Nanaimo Harbour, 29th March 1901 (revised 1961), 4197; blad
              - 576: Alden Bank to Nanaimo, 1st February 1952 (last correction 1957), 4198; blad
              - 579: Burrard Inlet to Cape Mudge, 21st December 1951 (last correction 1957), 4199; blad
              - 587: Isla Coiba to Bahia Manzanillo, 30th December 1882 (revised 1961), 4200; blad
              - 590: San Pablo Bay, Mare Island Strait, 27th June 1952 (last correction 1958), 4201; blad
              - 591: San Francisco Harbour, 12th December 1952 (revised 1963), 4202; blad
              - 592: San Francisco Bay - southern part, 27th June 1952 (revised 1962), 4203; blad
              - 660: Puerto Culebra, Corinto Harbour, Bahia Jiquilisco, Acajutla anchorage, 2nd April 1927 (last correction 1966), 4204; blad
              - 660: Harbours on the west coast of Central America, 4th April 1980 (revised 1983), 4205; blad